This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I want to take you to?
Let's head for it then!
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
Yeahhhhhhh!
They are developing extremely quick.
All four of these children
have incredible skill.
Oh, I can't get one more!
I'm so proud of you all!
Yeahhhhh!
My little masterpieces.
They have us make such lavish food.
But where did they take it all?
Huh, I don't know.
We haven't had any guests lately.
Stop being so nosy.
Our job is to cook the food,
not to ask questions about it.
All right.
Sanji!
I thought I told you royalty
doesn't serve anyone!
She's dead, and you know that!
So stop trying to be like your mother!
What happened are you all right there
master Sanji huh his majesty ordered
us not to allow you into the kitchen
oh please I beg you let me stay
Ha ha!
All finished!
Where are you going all by yourself?
To see my mother.
But the weather is awful!
And the medical ward is so
far! I'm fine! But wait!
Stop following me!
Don't tell my dad, okay?
Take shelter now!
Go away, dog!
I didn't make this food for you!
No!
Oh!
Oh, Master Sanji, you came here alone?
This was very thoughtful of you, my dear.
But I worry a meal like this
will upset Her Majesty's stomach.
Although, maybe it doesn't
taste as bad as it looks.
Sanji, it's pouring, and
you still came to see me?
Your father will be so
furious if he finds out.
Hear, your majesty.
He brought this for you.
Sweetheart, did you make this food?
Ebony?
What's wrong, my queen?
Don't be presumptuous.
Please bring me the food
Sanji really made at once.
Well, I would,
but you see, it got ruined on the way
over here and there was no salvaging it.
So I threw it away.
Bring it in right.
Look at that!
There's omelet rolls with
some fish and a banana, too.
Oh, mom.
I'm sorry I messed it up.
I was running and I tripped in the street.
It got smooshed and it's
all soggy, too Let's try
Yummy!
Really? Really?
Thanks, Mom!
Will you cook for me some more?
I... I...
I...
I miss you both!
Will you cook for me some more?
You want me to bring
you stuff to cook with?
The all-blue, a place with
fish from all four seas,
legendary waters.
Look at that, told you, it's him.
Right, that is Sanji.
He's still alive, huh?
But why would Dad lie
about something like that?
Because he wishes he was dead.
Hey, if Sanji really did die, I wonder if
Dad would be happy when he heard the news.
Hahaha!
Let me go.
You've always been a failure, Sanji.
You deserve to die.
You suck.
Don't think I'm on your side
just because I patched you up.
I'm not involved, okay?
Those three don't get sad.
They never feel sympathy either.
Father thinks they're such great fighters
because they don't have emotions.
My body has some physical modifications,
too, but I actually have emotions.
Bye.
Um, thanks for helping me again.
Oh, I think we're supposed to
cross over the red line soon.
Towards the East Blue.
We're going to fight in some wars.
Wars?
The time has come to
depart for the East Blue.
The estimated travel time is three weeks.
I want to be a cook, no
matter what it takes!
Fire!
Jeremiah Double Six is here! What?
They actually exist?
What's all the commotion?
Your Majesty!
Seems Koshia's soldiers noticed
us before we were able to strike!
Then subdue them!
I told you not to tell me stuff like that!
If I can just run away somehow,
while we're in the East Blue,
then I'll be free, right?
I can live the rest of my life
without ever seeing Dad's face again.
Back away!
You only get one chance!
So try not to mess it up!
Attack now!
The fight just started.
Father's hiding the key to
your mask in his bedroom,
so you need to go in
there and get it quickly.
What?
I'll check outside to see if
it's safe enough for you to go.
Okay, yeah.
As soon as you get to father's room,
look for a symbol on the
wall that looks like a skull.
That's where you'll find the secret door.
Gotcha!
What do you think you're doing?
You little brat.
How did you escape?
Speak up!
Father!
I'm going to leave this wretched kingdom,
and no one's getting in
my way, not even you!
You've developed quite an attitude
since you've been locked away.
You're normal, and that makes you weak.
There's not a sea in this entire world
where you can survive on your own.
You'll die.
yes what you still can't
stop me I wouldn't want
to it feels strange to
admit this but I suppose I
am human after all even
though my son is useless
I can't bring myself to
kill him but you're saying
you'll go away voluntarily
i won't stop you then
and i'll gladly let you
have the key to that iron
mask listen sanji before
you and i part ways for
the last time there is
something i must ask of you
No matter what,
if anyone ever asks about your family, you
must never tell them who your father is.
Having you as a son is my greatest shame.
You must know that.
I don't know.
What about the cruise ship at the port?
It's got nothing to do with us.
They were just unlucky to be here.
Let them be.
You need to board that ship.
Come on, Sanji.
Stop crying like a little baby.
Look!
You can never come back here, understand?
You'll be okay!
I swear!
The sea is really big.
You will meet nice
people out there someday.
Now go!
And don't look back!
Run away!
Run, Dash!
Oh, yum, these are good! Good! Nice work!
That son of a bird is eating the biscuits!
It's crazy!
Why would you even think
to do that, you freak?
Because biscuits are food and I'm hungry!
That's right, Luffy!
And the best way to get rid
of food is to eat it all up!
So dig in and don't stop!
This Fraulein is tremendously crafty, ya!
This looks really bad.
Did they knock him out?
Get out of my way.
Lady Race, we were just
going to give him treatment.
I said, get out of my way! I'm sorry!
Pathetic.
Are you going to meet your
fiancé with that face?
All you had to do was
give up on that old chef.
Then you wouldn't have
to suffer like this.
Why did you come back?
It makes no sense.
You said that you wanted to
forget this place. Sanji.
I think I might actually be full now.
You should be.
Hey, we've been at this forever.
I'm so sick of fighting you.
You eat, you run away.
You come back and eat some more.
Is this Straw Hat guy even human?
General Cracker may be scary, but that
guy's appetite is the real terror.
My General Cracker.
So with his power, he really can
keep making biscuits forever?
Yeah.
Just wait.
He'll run out of energy soon enough.
Not before you do.
Go ahead and keep eating.
You'll give up on your friend
when you're doubled over in pain.
No, I'm never gonna give up.
I'm gonna eat and eat and then
I'll go rescue Soji. That's so.
I'll bring out more biscuit
warriors for you then.
Are you ready?
Keep eating till you pop.
I don't care.
As for you, King Baum,
Mama is going to be very disappointed when
I tell her about your untimely betrayal.
What?
Shearing off mine branches
wasn't cool enough?
That's not fair, my general.
This Fraulein has Mama's Weaver card.
She's using us power to
make us bow down to her.
So technically it's Mama's
power we are obeying.
Save your excuses for her then Cause
I'll never forgive you bastards for this
This would be over if you
hadn't helped that insufferable
woman My biscuit warriors
are supposed to be invincible
And now look at them reduced
to yummy crunchy snacks all
thanks to you Stop your whining
This is a pirate battle, isn't it?
So what if I figured out your weakness?
That doesn't mean you get to take
it out on my underlings, okay?
Ha-ha! Ha-ha! Underlings!
Is that really what we've been reduced to?
Is that a problem?
No, ma 'am! Sorry! Hmph!
Let's put an end to this!
Biscuit warriors!
It's over, Straw Hat.
They come right back
when I break them apart.
So far, eating's all that's worked.
But, uh...
I'm not really hungry anymore.
Make sure to protect me, homies, or else!
Yes, ma 'am!
Hey, Nami!
Can we try something
other than eating them?
There's got to be a way to
stop them from reforming!
Weather egg, go!
Your boss may be an emperor, but
I don't know you and I don't care!
Luffy won't lose, because he's
going to be king of the pirates!
In other words, there's
no limit to his appetite!
Come on!
I've been eating all night long still he
hungers, his stomach's like a black hole.
Please.
Oh, do it, Tanchi!
This is for you!
Oh, please don't let me!
Lord Judge.
We're ready, all preparations are
complete here as well, good now.
Inform my children—we're
departing for the whole cake Shit.
Ready this'll hurt!
Just put it on already.
Barely tingles,
the
swelling
has
gone
down.
Swelling is the only thing the mask fixes;
it suppresses the body's
natural response to
an injury but it actually
slows your recovery.
It's
better than showing a face like
that to your fiancee though.
The charlotte family never
takes their spouse's last name.
You won't be a vinsmoke anymore if you get
along well enough—you
might live a happy life.
Shut up!
I don't know what you're
expecting from me.
You came here on your own.
your own
Here's a question.
Where did that chivalry come from?
Women! Women! Women! Women! Women!
Not a chance!
I am not hiring any ladies here!
Shut the hell up!
You know I punctuate my lessons
with a swift kick to the face.
I can't very well treat a woman that way.
And why not?
If you can kick me, then
you can kick a girl, too.
You little fool!
What did I say?
Listen up!
A man must never kick a lady.
That's been the golden rule
since the age of the dinosaurs.
You understand me?
All right, here's the deal.
As a human, you're gonna make mistakes.
That's only natural.
But as a man, if you ever
stray from the honorable path,
then I'll chop off your
balls as punishment!
and slit my own throat
while I'm at it. What?
Why would you slit your own throat?
Because as a parent, I gotta
take responsibility too.
Don't become the kind of person I hate.
That's all I'm saying.
Now get back to work, why don't you?
The Golden Rule from the Age of Dinosaurs.
Huh?
May I enter, please?
Sanji, sir, it's time to depart.
You have an engagement ceremony
to attend at the Whole Cake Shit.
Here, you'd better put on a clean shirt.
You're a member of the
royal family after all.
You need to present yourself like
a Vinsmoke or we'll look bad.
Like I give a crap.
Meanwhile, in Brule's mirror world...
Looks like I found you!
You found me!
You'll never escape me!
I don't think I can run anymore, Chumper!
If you trip and break a mirror,
your luck's gonna get even worse.
Have a wonderful wedding!
Good luck, Sanji, sir!
Congratulations!
And so begins a new era
for the Vinsmoke family.
Sanji, sir!
Wave to the citizens now, Sanji. Go on.
All right, guys!
Set sail!
Enough is enough, you bastards!
No more biscuits, everybody go home, OK?
So you're finally full. I'm full,
but I'm holding all those biscuits I ate
in my stomach if it's the last thing I do.
I don't need you to throw up to win this.
I'll just pop you right open.
Careful, Loopy!
Joke's on you!
I'm stuffed with power!
Muscle Balloon!
What the hell?!
Fourth gear, go!
I call this form Tank
Man Stuffed Vergeing!
Oh wow, he's huge!
That's got kind of a different
feel than your last transformation,
but can you even move because
you look pretty bloated to me?
General Cracker's blade can't cut out!
What's this guy made out of?
I've had enough of you,
you stubborn little pest.
You've pushed me over the edge, Stryhat.
It's over.
Time to die!
If I can't cut you, then
I'll stab you instead! Honey!
Brunzo!
One more!
I'll burst you open this
time, mark my words!
Crash pretzel!
Lupi, are you okay?
Uh, uh, what?
His skin is hard, but it's soft, too?
Damn it!
I can't pull away!
Biscuit warriors!
Rain Spark!
Nami!
Don't get the biscuits wet!
I have a different plan this time!
And I need them to stay hard!
Look! I can't move!
What's he trying to do?
I'm gonna show you the power
of me on a full stomach!
Time for you to fly!
I'll send you to the far
ends of the new world!
Dog-gog cannonball!
No more biscuits!
Oh, my God.